Privacy Policy
==============

We at Second Baptist Church understand the spiritual benefits of the Internet and the tremendous ministry opportunities afforded by its use. We also understand the importance of respecting and protecting your privacy.

#### INFORMATION COLLECTED AND HOW IT IS USED

Second Baptist Church collects two types of information when you visit our web site:

1. Personal Information  
    This is information that you voluntarily supply to us through a visitor registration card, email or the Second Baptist Church website. It is information that you provide us for such things as prayer requests, online purchases, volunteering for Second Baptist ministries, church membership, etc. All personal information is kept confidential and is not distributed, sold, or shared with anyone. It is strictly used for the purposes of allowing Second Baptist Church to encourage you in your walk with Jesus Christ.

2. Technical Information  
    This is information that is exchanged between our computer and yours when visiting our website. This information is anonymous and cannot personally identify you. This type of information includes, but is not limited to, your IP address, referring URL, type of Web browser, browser display settings, and whether you are a first time visitor or returning visitor to the site. We may place a "cookie" on your computer, which is used to recognize you when you visit our site. The technical information gathered from those visiting our site allows us to improve the usability of the website and reduce the number of problems that may occur when viewing our site. If you have questions about the use of personal and technical information collected through our website, you may contact us by email at support@second.org.

#### INFORMATION

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. They are used to allow web servers to recognize the computer used to access a web site. They allow Second Baptist Church to simplify subsequent visits and to enhance your personal experience in using our web site. Most computers are set up to automatically receive cookies. However, you can prevent cookies from being placed on your computer by going to your web browser's preferences menu. Cookies are not used to gain any personal information about you.

#### USES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

Any information that Second Baptist Church collects and that you provide is strictly used to extend the ministry of our church. We do not sell, lease, or distribute any information to any commercial entities. Second Baptist Church may offer services such as chat rooms, message boards, or other open discussion forums. **Be aware that any information that you supply in such forums is considered public information and is not protected**.

#### LINKS

This web site may contain links to other sites. Second Baptist Church does not endorse or receive any financial benefit from the entities for which links are provided. Links to third party entities and related materials and information are provided only as a ministry. These sites may not be owned or operated by Second Baptist Church and we are not responsible for the privacy policies or information collection practices of these sites. The Privacy Policy of Second Baptist Church does not apply to such third parties and they are responsible for their own privacy statements. We encourage you to be aware of the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

#### SECURITY

The security of the information that you provide to us is very important to Second Baptist Church. Therefore, this web site takes every precaution to protect this information. For added security, all sensitive personal information is protected by SSL (Secure Socket Layer). We will attempt to notify you as soon as possible if our security system is breached and data is compromised.

#### CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

We at Second Baptist Church are strongly committed to the safety and protection of children. Second Baptist Church, through its website, does not knowingly accept or collect personal information (such as name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, social security number, credit card information, date of birth, zip code, and any other information that would allow personal identification) from children under the age of 13 without the prior written verifiable consent from the parent(s) or guardian. Second Baptist Church does not disclose any information collected from children to third parties.

Terms of Use
============

Welcome to Second.org. We provide services to you subject to the following terms. If you visit Second.org, you accept these terms. Please read them carefully.

#### ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS

When you visit Second.org or send emails to us, you are communicating with us electronically. You consent to receive communications from us electronically. We will communicate with you by email or by posting notices on this site. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.

#### COPYRIGHT, LICENSE AND SITE ACCESS

All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, digital downloads, data compilations, and software, is the property of the Second Baptist Church or its content suppliers and protected by United States and international copyright laws. The compilation of all content on this site is the exclusive property of Second.org and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. All software used on this site is the property of the Second Baptist Church or its software suppliers and protected by United States and international copyright laws. This site or any portion of this site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without express written consent of Second Baptist Church. You may not frame or utilize framing techniques to enclose any trademark, logo, or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout, or form) of Second.org. You may not use any meta tags or any other "hidden text" utilizing Second Baptist's name or trademarks without the express written consent of Second Baptist Church. Any unauthorized use terminates the permission or license granted by Second Baptist Church. You are granted a limited, revocable, and nonexclusive right to create a hyperlink to the home page of Second.org so long as the link does not portray Second.org in a false, misleading, derogatory, or otherwise offensive matter. You may not use any Second Baptist Church logo or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part of the link without express written permission. You may not use Second Baptist Church logo on any third party website or on class websites / leadership portal hosted by Second Baptist Church.

#### YOUR ACCOUNT

If you use this site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. If you are under 18, you may use Second.org only with involvement of a parent or guardian. Second.org reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content at their sole discretion.

#### PRAYER REQUESTS, COMMUNICATIONS, AND OTHER CONTENT

Visitors may post prayer requests and other communications so long as the content is not illegal, obscene, threatening, defamatory, invasive of privacy, infringing of intellectual property rights, or otherwise injurious to third parties or objectionable and does not consist of or contain software viruses, political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings, or any form of "spam." You may not use a false email address, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead as to the origin of a prayer request or other content. Second.org reserves the right (but not the obligation) to remove or edit such content.

#### BIBLE STUDY CLASS LEADERSHIP PORTAL

Each adult Bible Study class of Second Baptist Church has the opportunity to use the leadership portal (also known as “class site”) as an extension of second.org. These sites are hosted on Second Baptist Church servers and are governed by the Terms of Use and Privacy Policies of second.org. Select individuals from each class are granted permissions by Second Baptist Church to maintain the content contained within each class portal. Second Baptist Church reserves the right at any time to remove a class portal or any part of its content. By creating a login and using the leadership portal, you agree not to use the portal or the personal information contained within for any solicitations including but not limited to solicitations of one's personal business or employer, solicitations for personal financial assistance or assistance on behalf of another, and solicitations for mission activities not sponsored by Second Baptist Church. You also agree to not publish any information that promotes, recommends, or references political candidates or political organizations. By using the leadership portal, you agree not to post pictures that are pornographic, sexually inappropriate or suggestive, and misrepresentative of the values and teachings of Second Baptist Church.

#### DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES AND LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

THIS SITE IS PROVIDED BY SECOND.ORG ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. SECOND.ORG MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THIS SITE OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, OR PRODUCTS INCLUDED ON THIS SITE. YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THIS SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY APPLICABLE LAW, SECOND.ORG DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. SECOND.ORG DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THIS SITE, ITS SERVERS, OR EMAIL SENT FROM SECOND.ORG AND SECONDFAMILY.ORG ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. SECOND.ORG WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF THIS SITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. CERTAIN STATE LAWS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN DAMAGES. IF THESE LAWS APPLY TO YOU, SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE DISCLAIMERS, EXCLUSIONS, OR LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, AND YOU MIGHT HAVE ADDITIONAL RIGHTS.

#### APPLICABLE LAW

By visiting Second.org, you agree that the laws of the state of Texas, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern these Terms of Use and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and Second Baptist Church.

#### YOUR CONSENT

By using this web site, you are giving Second Baptist Church your express consent to use the information collected about you as this policy outlines.

#### QUESTIONS

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, please feel free to contact us:

Technology Ministry  
Second Baptist Church  
6400 Woodway  
Houston, TX 77057  
support@second.org  
713-465-3408

SMS Policy
==========

By subscribing, you have provided us with consent to send you text messages regarding Second Baptist Church or The Winning Walk events. Message frequency varies by events/preference. Message and data rates may apply. Carriers are not liable for delayed or undeliverable messages. If your phone does not support MMS, you’ll receive SMS instead.

#### OPT-OUT OR STOP

If you wish to stop receiving text messages from Second Baptist church or The Winning Walk, reply to any text message and in the reply, text STOP. You may also stop text messages by calling us at 713-465-3408 or emailing us at [support@second.org](mailto:support@second.org "mailto:support@second.org"). 

#### HELP OR SUPPORT

If at any time you need our contact information on how to stop text messages, reply to any of our text messages and in the reply, text HELP. Upon receiving your text message, we will send you a text message with this information. In general, the messages we send provide you with information about our upcoming events, new content, and other announcements. Some of the text messages we send may include links to websites. To access these websites, you will need a web browser and internet access.

#### SUPPORTED CARRIERS

This program is supported by Alltel, AT&T, Boost, Sprint, Verizon Wireless, Virgin Mobile, MetroPCS, T-Mobile and U.S. Cellular. T-Mobile is not liable for delayed or undeliverable messages. Products and services are compatible with AT&T handsets.

#### PRIVACY POLICY

We respect your privacy and will not distribute your mobile phone number to any third parties.

© Second Baptist Church 2020 • [Privacy Policy](https://www.second.org/privacy-policy/) • [Term of Use](https://www.second.org/privacy-policy/#terms-of-use)  
Site design by [Creative Element](http://creative-element.com/)

* 
* Interested in giving online or managing your existing giving account?
    
*   
* © 2019 Copyright Second Baptist Church  
    All rights reserved
